sportclips.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy | Sport Clips

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy explains our use of any personal information you may supply Sport Clips, Inc. ("SCI") when visiting our websites or stores owned by SCI or using the SCI mobile application. 

We recognize and respect the privacy of our clients, visitors and users of our mobile application. We do not collect personal information about visitors to our websites or stores owned by SCI or users of our mobile application unless it is provided voluntarily. Our goal in collecting personal information online or in stores owned by SCI or on our mobile application is to provide you with relevant information that meets your specific needs and to ensure that your visit to our websites or stores owned by SCI or your use of the mobile application is efficient and productive.

**Types of Information We Collect and How It Is Used**

SCI only gathers personal information, such as, first and last names, addresses and email addresses, when you voluntarily provide that information to us. Personal information may be collected from you in order to ask for your feedback on our websites, mobile application, products or services, or to enter you in one of our prize promotions. In addition, we collect location information with your permission if you choose to use the Online Check In feature of the web site or the mobile application. (If you use a mobile device and have provided permission, location information will also be collected even if you do _not_ choose to use the Online Check In feature.) At stores owned by SCI, personal information also includes your credit or debit card number and related information (e.g., card expiration date) if used to pay for service(s) purchased at that store. In all cases, unless otherwise expressly indicated herein, personal information will only be used by SCI for the specific purpose for which it was collected. 

**Sharing of Personal Information**

SCI is a franchising company, and we may share personal information within the Sport Clips System. The Sport Clips System includes Sport Clips, Inc., our area developers, our franchisees, and our affiliates. Parties in the Sport Clips System may have access to your personal information, but we direct each party in the Sport Clips System to comply with our Privacy Policy. Occasionally, with your permission, we will send marketing information to you, such as discount coupons or information about new services. If you elect not to receive such materials, we will no longer send them to you.

Companies may be hired by SCI to perform a variety of functions, such as assisting with promotions or providing technical services for our websites, mobile application, etc. (At stores owned by SCI, such companies also include entities that assist SCI in facilitating and processing credit card/debit card transactions.) These companies may have access to personal information if needed to perform these functions. However, our direction to these companies is that they may only use such personal information for the purpose of performing that function and may not use it for any other purpose; furthermore, such companies have agreed to maintain the confidentiality of such information.

We may, on occasion, share personal information to approved third parties for marketing purposes on behalf of our franchisees or stores owned by SCI. SCI does not sell or disclose personal information to third parties outside the Sport Clips System. Upon request, you may elect to receive a copy, and/or update your personal information from our electronic systems through our Contact Us page. SCI reserves the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request, to protect the integrity of our websites, mobile application, to fulfil your requests, or to cooperate in any law enforcement investigation or an investigation on a matter of public safety.

**Access**

  1. If at any time, you would like to opt out of further electronic communication (i.e., e-mail) from us or the Sports Clips System, you can let us know by contacting us at click here or at the postal address listed below. 

Sport Clips, Inc.

Attn: Privacy

110 Briarwood Dr.

Georgetown, Texas 78628

  1. If at any time, you would like to opt out of further text message communications from us or the Sports Clips System, you can let us know by texting STOP. (You may, however, receive one [1] additional text message confirming your decision to unsubscribe.)
  2. If at any time, you would like to opt out of “push notifications” (i.e., notifications sent to you from the mobile application when it is _not_ open), modify your consent settings on your mobile device.
  3. If at any time, you would like to disable the collection of location information, modify your consent settings on your mobile device.

**Cookies**

"Cookies" are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies allow the website to remember important information that will make your use of our websites more convenient. Like most websites, SCI uses cookies for a variety of purposes in order to improve your on-line experience. For example, we track the total number of visitors to our websites on an anonymous aggregate basis. We may also employ cookies so that we remember you when you return to the website, to administer certain contests and sweepstakes, or to help customize your Sport Clips web experience. We may associate personal information with a cookie file in those instances.

Use the options in your web browser if you do not wish to receive a cookie or if you wish to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. Click on the "Help" section of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. Please be advised that if you choose to disable cookies, this will limit your access to certain features or functionality of the website, thereby affecting your experience in using the website.

Kindly note, too, that we may also utilize cookies on mobile devices. 

**Children’s Privacy**

This website and mobile application are intended for general audiences and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 at the website or via the mobile application. If we become aware of collecting personal information on the website or mobile application from any child under the age of 13, we will immediately delete such personal information. If a parent or legal guardian believes that his/her child under the age of 13 has provided personal information on the website or mobile application, please contact us at privacy@SportClips.com or at the postal address set forth above.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Under California law, California residents may request details as to how their information is shared by SCI with third parties for direct marketing purposes. (Such third parties include individual Sport Clips salons operated by franchisees.) California residents may request this information once per calendar year by contacting us at privacy@SportClips.com or at the postal address set forth above. 

**Links to Other Websites**

From time to time, we may post links to other websites owned and operated by third parties. We have no control over the content or the policies of these websites. If you visit the linked website, you should check the privacy policy of that web site.

**Franchisee Websites and Stores**

Most Sport Clips salons are owned and operated by franchisees, who are independent businessmen and women. Some franchisees may also operate independent websites. We have no control over the content of these websites, nor the policies of these stores and websites as to the collection, sharing or use of personal information. If you visit a website that is owned and operated by an independent Sport Clips franchisee, please review the privacy policy of that website to determine the privacy policy of that website. If you visit a store that is owned and operated by an independent Sport Clips franchisee, you may inquire regarding their in-store information collection policies.

**Miscellaneous**

SCI will only store information collected via this Privacy Policy for as long as is necessary to perform the corresponding function and/or to comply with applicable legal requirements. By using the website or mobile application, you agree to SCI storing and process this information in the United States.  SCI uses administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against unauthorized use or disclosure of personal information; however, we caution that no safeguard is fool-proof or provides absolute protection against unauthorized use/disclosure of personal information.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy is effective as of 2-28-19, as revised and updated. From time to time, it may be necessary for SCI to change this privacy policy. If we change our policy, we will post the revised version here. Any changes will not be applied retroactively, and will not change how we handle previously collected information.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about SCI's privacy policy, please contact us at privacy@SportClips.com
